How are you doing?
I am Mizuki Fukumura, sub-leader of Morning Musume。 s sub-leader, Mizuki Fukumura.
I will be your MC this time. Please give me your best regards.
I am 16 years old now, but I will turn 17 on October 30.
My hobby is taking pictures of elevator buttons and collecting them,
Thanks for watching this video.
Hallo! This time, I'm going to meet Mizuki Fukumura, a member of Morning Musume。 23's Mizuki Fukumura and
Rina Ikuta from Morning Musume。 23, and Rina Ikuta from Morning Musume。
Mizuki Fukumura is going to be the last MC for Hallo! I'm Mizuki Fukumura, the last MC for Halo!
I was wearing my favorite outfit at that time.
I was wearing my favorite dress at that time... and what I was saying was the same.
It's surprising to see the two of us MCing at the Halloween party. It's also the first time for the two of us to MC at Halo!
I hope we can do what only the two of us can do.
And now, Morning Musume。 23 Concert Tour Autumn Neverending Employee of the Year Award.
How are you feeling right now? How are you feeling right now?
I can't believe it, but I'm having so much fun on this fall tour.
I don't remember when a month went by so fast... but I'm having so much fun, and it's so rewarding and fun.
I feel like I'm having a lot of fun, and I'm having a lot of fun, and I'm having a lot of fun, and I'm having a lot of fun, and I'm having a lot of fun.
I'd like to cherish the moments when I make eye contact with the members or when I have a call and response with the fans even more.
Personally, with the Corona Disaster, I've been in a situation where I couldn't speak and couldn't stand up.
I feel like we're finally back to a normal world where it's okay to speak up and the audience is allowed to stand.
It's finally back to the normal world where it's OK to shout and the audience is allowed to stand.
I'm personally happy to be able to welcome Mizuki's graduation performance in the usual way, with standing room only and with the ability to speak up.
I'm also very happy that we are going to have a new organization in the future.
How do you want us to see you in the future? It will be the first time to see the 14 of us at Yokohama Arena, and we will see Morning Musume with 13 members.
Well... I feel that I spent a very precious time during the past 6 months from when I joined the 17th term until my graduation.
I wonder what I want to tell the 17th term members about that. I wonder if I wouldn't have been able to tell them if I hadn't decided to graduate.
I have told them things that I think I might not have been able to tell them if I hadn't decided to graduate.
I hope that they will inherit my impression of Morning Musume, but I also hope that when I see the 17th term in about six months, my impression of them will be very different.
I personally think that the members I see up close and the members I see from afar with an objective view are different. I personally think that the members I see up close are different from the members I see from afar with an objective view.
I hope that all of you fans will continue to love Morning Musume even after there are 14 of us and 13 of Mizuki, too.
Let's see the video!
A
I love you.
Say "I love you.
You have to say it out loud.
That's great, my friend.
I still love you.
I still love you
Do it!
One love, no regrets, no regrets
I still love you, I still love you, I still love you
Saddened by the sorrow of others
Do it! Do it! Do it!
There's no estimate of life out there
Jealousy
Love is boring
Covetousness is a form of love
Sad
Acting in love
No one can get him drunk
Everybody clap your hands
Everybody clap
It's got to be my last life
I can't do it anymore
Everybody clap your hands
Everybody clap
It's time to make the most of your time
You'll see. I'm gonna find out.
It's starting.
Romance on the way
Let's grab it
Romance forever
Oh, it's gonna be endless
Dancing in my dreams
The future's in your hands
I'm gonna change it
It's just a little too hard
And you'll get over it
Say I love you
Say it loud and clear.
Can't you say it out loud?
Score your back
I still love you the year
Early summer, love you, love you
Do it!
It's starting
Gjob of romance
Isn't it nice to fall in love with a stranger?
We all lose it at first
Years. It's supposed to be longer than the years.
I'm sure you don't want to talk about the old days, do you?
I love you
No, thank you
I'm in heaven
You look as shy as you laugh
I'm practicing for the love of my dreams
Sometimes tomorrow night is niceSometimes I like tomorrow night.
Everybody clap your hands!
Everybody dance!
To the sound of my heart pounding
Mango Network
Everybody clap your hands
Everybody dance!
Singing live as we go
The curtain drops and the days go by
Let the days begin
In the middle of romance
No more time
Romance's honors
Oh, and so weightless
Let's dance, let's dance, let's dance
See you next time.
Yes!
It's like we never stop.
There's something happening
Jump over this song
Say I love you.
Hekili, I have to say it out loud.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
I still love you
Yeah.
I still love you.
To end to end
I still love you
--Kumari no 39 Technical
Oh, say I love youOh, say I love you.
I have to say it out loud.
Oh, my God.
I still love you.
I still love you
Do it!
Say I still love you
I still love you
I still love you Yeah
Do it
It's starting, the halfway point of romance
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for your work!
This is Mizuki Fukumura and Rina Ikuta from Morning Musume。
Rina Ikuta from Morning Musume。 Sten.
From here, we'd like to talk a little about each other.
I'm going to ask you a few questions, so don't think too much and answer in a quick tempo.
What do you think you have left to do in the year 2023?
Well, I wanted to sing a little more solo.
Morning Musume。23 Concert Tour Autumn Neverending Employees Show Special on November 28th.
What are you personally looking forward to?
Well, the collaboration between OG seniors and current members.
What is the best word to describe Morning Musume。23 right now?
Greed?
It's the last day on earth.
What would you like to eat?
I don't know.What is it?
Yakitori
Last one.
Hello! Project celebrates its 25th anniversary this year!
Which song is indispensable for Rina Ikuta?
I miss you Lonely Christmas
Ummm...
Thank you very much.
I lied.
I like Lil Puri.
Lil' Puri.
Lil' Puri, okay.
I'd like to see what Morning Musume。 I want it to represent
Greed
Personally, I have a lot of desires that I want to do this and that.
I want to do this and do that, but lately I've been seeing that everyone wants to do this and do that, too.
I want to change things and change the future, in that sense as well.
It's better to have it often.
Then, what is another song that is indispensable for Rina Ikuta?
Lil Puri.
Yes, Lil' Puri.
This is the song I sang in the third round.
The third round?
Mizuki sang it.
There were about 13 songs.
And out of those 13 songs, you could choose your favorite song.
Everyone chose songs by Berryz KOBO, Morning Musume。 or Morning Musume。
and so on.
So Eri sang the Lil' Puri song and then sang an anime song, and that was probably the only song Eri sang that day.
Eri was probably the only one who sang that day.The only person who sang that day was probably Eri.
Hmmm...
Well, I was accepted in the third round.
And we were able to go to the camp with that song.
Yeah...
I kind of miss her... it was like a Lonely Christmas.
but I thought Lil' Puri was more like the song that started me off
So I went with that one.
The question for Mizuki was after the VTR.
Hallo! STE!
That's great!
That one lie can be the end of everything.
Morning Musume。23 す すごいフィバー！!
Now on sale!
Wake up call It's time to wake up
It's time to enjoy life
To the sun's light, to the invitation
Wake up call It's time to wake up Now on sale!
If you say it like that, then I'll say it like that... Humans are just a bunch of stupid moms
Morning Musume。23 featuring Mizuki Fukumura
Never ending shine Now on sale!
Cross the red line, get hurt, get hurt, I want to hurt you
I do I do Ai no tamer
Angulum Red Line December 13 on sale!
Life with my mouth is open and full in the sky
It's so much fun, I'm in a hurry, it's a game
Angulum Life is beautiful December 13 on sale!
Halo! Sta.
Next, I would like to ask Mizuki a question.
Yes, I do.Yes, ma'am.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
And now, Morning Musume。 23.
Mizuki Fukumura's last photo book, Last Scene, is now on sale.
If I were to write my own catchphrase for this photo book...
It contains all of me!
For Mizuki Fukumura, Morning Musume。 For Mizuki Fukumura, Morning Musume。
It's my life!
What do you expect from the next Morning Musume。 What do you expect from the next Morning Musume。
There are a lot of things to look forward to, but potential
Possibilities?
Then...
What song would you most like to see after you graduate?
Morning Musume。 Morning Musume。
Yeah.
Wow, I don't know.
Songs you want to see performed
I want to show you with him.
Ooh.
Well then, let's see what Hello! Project songs of all time that you've been impressed by performing on stage.
Wow Everyday is on a roll!
So, if we're going to play catch-up, it's going to be a photo book.
Where do you think it all began?
I feel like it's really the culmination of everything I've done.
This is my eighth book.
It's amazing.
I've tried a lot of different shapes and sizes.
I've tried all kinds of shapes, but this is the first time I've used beige in my outfits.
You can also see my daily life.And then there's the part where you can see my daily life.
I don't know... it's a compilation of all the photos I've taken up to this point, plus a little bit of my everyday life.
You can see a part of my daily life.
I've tried to show colors and ways that are close to my true self.
And there are also interviews.
So the whole book is kind of like my life.
Oh, I see.
I feel like it's all there.
I feel like it's all in there.
So what's next on your list of things to look forward to?
Yeah, I'm looking forward to Morning Musume。 Morning Musume。
Rio Sakurai is now in her second year.
The 17th term members are in their first year.
They've only been in the group for six months.
I think they still have a lot of growth potential.
I don't want to make any assumptions.
Don't make assumptions about who is good at what kind of things.
I think this is the year for them to grow up.
I'm looking forward to the path that the younger members are going to open up.
And the older members will soon be over 10 years old.
And the 12th term members are going to pass the 10 years mark.
I wonder what it is.
I'm looking forward to seeing the path that the younger members are going to open up.
I'm looking forward to seeing what they can do both as a group and as a solo artist.
I'd like you to go forward more and more as a group
I'd like you to go forward as a group and as a solo artist.
I think that the group will be filled with various possibilities.
I see. Thank you very much.
So, thank you very much for your time. Please look forward to the rest of the show!
Natsuyaki ni Abi desu!Summer Yaki ni Abi!
Here we are at Hello Kitchen!
This time, we have a member here!
This is Momo Kitahara of Ocha no Oma!
Momo will do her best!
I'm looking forward to working with you!
So cute!
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Mr. Ube, I'm looking forward to working with you today.
I look forward to working with you.
Nice to meet you.
What would you like to make this time?
I would like to make mushroom risotto.
Mushroom risotto menu is like this.
Do you usually cook, Momochan?
I, Kitahara, don't cook at all.
I don't cook at all.
I've always wanted to be a chef.
I've been secretly looking forward to seeing you on Hello Kitchen.
I've been secretly looking forward to it.
I'm very happy.
I'll do my best.
Let's work hard and make it delicious!
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's see what we're going to make first.
First of all, onions.
Onions.
Chopped, this may be the most difficult part of the day.
KnifeA kitchen knife.
Kitchen knife.
Are you sure about the knife?
No, I don't really use a knife.
chopping
Don't worry about it.
finely chopped
chopped
That's it... ads
advertisement
That's right.
Let's try it this time.
Take it easy.
Hands like this?
Like this.
Cat's paw.
A little bit closer to the body, a little bit closer to the body.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's good.
When you get to the middle, it's not safe again, so take it down.
Or you can take them one at a time.
That way it gets harder.
Take the knife off once.
They're stacked on top of each other, so it's dangerous.
If you take them one at a time like this, it's easier to hold them down.
Turn around like this.
And...
And...In.
In.
Yes, I got over the onion safely.
Yes, I got over the onion!
I don't need this part of the onion, so I just cut it off
I just cut it off here
Slide this one off, too.
Only the eringi mushrooms need to be cut.
I'm going to use half the amount of mushrooms this time.
Just before we started recording
You said you love mushrooms.
Yes, I love mushrooms!
So I'm glad to hear that, because I'm sure she'll be very relieved.
She was so relieved.
It's perfect.
It's all right!
Yay!
I'll never use a knife again.
I'll do the rest by hand...
On the contrary, you really shouldn't use a knife for this.
That's right.
It's good to tear...
Do you know what good bamboo is?
I love good bamboo.
That's what I'm talking about.
I do it myself all the time.
You said you liked miso soup.He said he likes miso soup.
I can make miso soup with maitake mushrooms.
Nice and homey.
Wow!
What do you do with the maitake then?
Just toss them in the miso soup.
That's right, just like that!
Pororo pororo!
It's okay if I take all of these off, too.
Yes.
Now let's cook the mushrooms.
Can you see the smoke coming out? Yes, you can.
Now the pan is very hot.
When it's hot, a little bit more olive oil.
It's important that there's a lot of oil, so you need to use a very high heat.
Now, Mr. Eringi, I'm gonna do this.
Oh, Mr. eringi, I'm on it.
Be careful. This is important.
Be careful
Don't touch it too much, just salt.
Oh, it's burnt!
Everyone hides it. Wait a minute.
This color is very important.
Yes, this is the miyamizu point.
Shift the mushrooms.
Make sure they're well browned.
Here we go.
And here it is. Like this.
They're browned, right?
It just bounces around. It's a lot of oil.It just bounces around. It's pretty greasy.
And now it's OK.
It's so beautifully burned, it's a nice color
I'll put it in a teaspoon of water.
I'll put a cigarette here once.
I'm turning off the heat now, so it won't bounce.
Now we're going to grill the mushrooms.
Shimeji mushrooms
And then...
And...
Try not to let the mushrooms overlap.
Yes...
As much as possible to hit this iron part
As evenly as possible
Yes, spread them out. They're flat.
If you do this together...
If you do it together, together, together, it faces this way.
If you do them together.
If you do them together, they don't get browned.
It's all browned at once.
Do you cook mushrooms? You don't cook mushrooms?
I don't cook much. I like to eat bread.
What do you like that your mother cooks?
Is it all good?
Everything is good.
There's still a lot of flavor here.
It was supposed to be white wine.
But I used cooking wine.
About a tablespoon.
It's dangerous.It's not safe here.
They're escaping from over here again.
If you light a fire and it evaporates...
A little slower.
Whoa!
It's on fire.
Now the alcohol is gone, so we're good.
I'd like you to take a look at this.
The oil and the alcohol and the mushrooms.
And the mushrooms.
The flavor of the mushrooms.
It's a little bit thick.
That's right.
That's the source of the flavor.
You mustn't throw it away.
Never throw it away.
That's an important point.
It's also very important.
It's a key point, right?
Yes, that's right.
Ube point.
I really want you to do it.
I wish you could do it.
What?
Ubechi Point.
It's so cute.
Or you could just say you don't want it.
No, I want it.
Please, one time.
Ubetsuchi point here. Ubechi point here.
Yes, sir.
What was that? Don't miss the flavor.
So cute!
Momochan's so cute!
Then do it. Let's use Momo-chan points for the next point.
I'll put it in the pot.
Okay.
Risotto is a soup that needs to be made once.
1.5 liters of water is a lot.
That's a lot of water.
Usually, rice and water are roughly 1.1 or so.
This is by far the largest amount.
It's like a stir-fry.
You let the rice absorb more and more of the broth.
But since it's done in a frying pan, the water evaporates rapidly.
One consommé
A little salt
A pinch of salt.
A pinch of salt
And you don't have to heat it up to a boil.
Here's a taste.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's hot.
It's a little hot.
Yes, it's hot.
It's hot.
Hot, isn't it?
Mmm.Mmm.
Oh, it tastes like mushrooms.
You do, don't you?
Yes, I do.
He grilled them earlier.
Oh, it's hot.
What about that? Not too salty?
Not too salty, just a little thin.
Thin?
Yes, sir.
Then it's okay.
It looks fine.
Just right.
It's got a little bit of fat in it, too.
Yes, it's floating.
It's a little bit dense. It's perfect.
So, that's all for this time.
Next time, we will finish it.
Yes, we will finish it next time.
So, let's do our best next time.
I'll do my best.
See you next time!
Bye bye!
Risotto in the amazing Chankojanku! It's turning into risotto!
Delicious!
It's not often you get to see the members cooking.
For some people, it's a thrill.
For some people, it's thrilling and for others, it makes them want to cook for them.
I love this corner!I like this corner.
You like it?
Miki Nonaka is a little bit of a bad cook in my house.
Nonaka said she spent the shortest amount of time ever using a knife.
She said that.
After that, we recorded Eri.
Eri didn't use a knife that much either.
Nonaka was probably too much.
The staff was applauding.
That's right.
Certainly Nonaka couldn't tell the difference between lettuce and cabbage.
That's about where he started.
I'm sure it was tough.
Does that mean you usually cook?
Yes.
It's necessary for survival.
What have you cooked lately?
I don't know.
But I cook regularly.
I hear you love stuffed peppers.
I think my stuffed peppers are the best in the world.
So I make stuffed peppers regularly.
I'd like to try it.
That's fine.
I'd love to have you come over.
I wonder what I'll make... lately I've been thinking about protein and other things.
I don't really cook much. I tend to just grill or something.
But when I do cook, I'm good at minestrone.
Call me a pain in the ass, but...
Cutting vegetables is a real pain in the ass.It's so annoying to cut vegetables.
But I love soup so much.
I like to create soups.
For example?
Spicy.
I don't know what it's called.
Like yukkijang.
Something like that.
And some vinegar.
It's my own style of Chinese soup.
If you're talking about Chinese soup...
I love thick Chinese soup.
You put potato starch in it.
When I go to a Chinese soup restaurant
I get so excited.
For a while, I was really into that.
Sludgy Chinese soup.
Because I make it myself
I can get the taste that strikes my fancy.
That's the beauty of cooking.
And it's fun to make something that tastes a little bit stronger.
It's fun.
It's fun, even if it's a little burnt.
You enjoy it.
I enjoy cooking.
I hope you'll invite me again.
I'll do my best.
Let's do our best tomorrow.
Mizuki Fukumura and Erina Ikuta of Morning Musume。 23 present "Halo! STE, presented by Mizuki Fukumura and Erina Ikuta of Morning Musume 23.Mizuki Fukumura and Erina Ikuta of Morning Musume。23 present "Halo! Ste.
Morning Musume。23 Concert Tour Autumn next Wednesday, November 29th at Yokohama Arena.
Neverending Employee Show Sanctuary: Mizuki Fukumura's Graduation Special will be held at Yokohama Arena next Wednesday, November 29.
I'd like to ask Mizuki a few questions about her upcoming graduation.
Well, you know, there's only one week left until graduation.
How do you feel?
You know, we're all graduating from now on.
I'd like to say something, but I really don't have time.
I've been thinking about this since June.
We've been working on it since June.
But right before the graduation, there was an overflow of work.
I've been working from morning till night.
I've been working from morning till night, so I haven't been able to finish at all.
Also, I'd like to write letters and stuff like that.
But I haven't finished that at all at this moment.
I don't know what to think about.
I don't know...
I wonder if I'm saying thank you to all the people I want to say thank you to.
I'm getting more and more anxious.
I don't know how to put it, but I'm in such a hurry.
Each day goes by so fast.
But I want to take each step forward.
I want to make sure that the time for the concert is just right.
I don't want to show that kind of rushed feeling
I don't want to show that kind of impatience.
I want to cherish the time I have with the members.
I want to finish my work at home.
I want to spend time with my members in a way that's important to me.
I want to spend time with the members.
I don't know how to put it.I don't know what I would say too much.
I don't really feel that I'm going to stop being a member of Morning Musume。 I still don't really feel that I'm not Morning Musume。
But for now...
I wrote "Morning Musume。23" before.
But it's the last time I'm going to write Morning Musume。
It's going to be my original name.
I'd like to say something now.
The other thing is that I felt the greatest sense of accomplishment in the activities.
A sense of accomplishment.
Wow, that's a tough one.
From the Budokan stage in the spring of 2015.
Oh, gradations?
Gradation?
The 9th term members became the most senior members.
And there were 4 of us who were in the same term.
I really felt like we were all in the same place at that time.
After Sayumi Michishige, the previous leader, graduated.
We felt insecure in various areas such as name recognition and ability.
I wondered if we would be suitable for this stage.
I wondered if we would fit in on this stage.
We were all very anxious.
Even in such a situation, I think we were all able to work together and do our best while aiming for the top.
We sang "Namidachi" at that time.
Everyone's cheers were so warm and I felt a great sense of accomplishment.
I felt a great sense of accomplishment.
Hallo! sta.
Eri, you know, Mizuki was the leader of this year's group in 2015, and in 2014, she was the leader of the group.
Mizuki was the leader in 2014, but in 2015, she was doing some real leader-like work, and up until that time, until Michishige-san was the leader, the senior members were the leaders, so it's not like it's just about what's going on.
I didn't know what was going on and how they were working, but now that one of my peers is leading, I feel like I'm getting a closer look at things.
I felt like I was able to see things more closely now that my peers were leading.She said something like, "You have to do something like that at a time like that.
Like at the fan club event, or when Mizuki was talking too much about mc, so she should do the talking.
Mizuki was also concerned about who wasn't talking.
So there's a lot of things that the fans don't see, so there's a lot of work that goes into it.
And the adults take care of that, so it was a lot of work at first, but gradually you get used to it.
I personally just watch, but...
I hope it will be easier for Eri to be involved in the activities by saying something or saying something.
I'm sure it was a lot of work.
To sum up...
In summary, I don't mind that it's been so long.
I was thinking how hard it must have been for you.
Lastly, do you have a message for the fans, the viewers, and the people who will be coming to the concert, the graduation concert at Yokohama Arena on the second day?
Yes, I've been performing for about 15 years, including my time as a member of Halo Pro Egg, so thank you very much for your support.
Thank you very much.
I don't really know what's going to happen to me now that I've been living with Morning Musume, but I never stopped thinking about it.
But because I never stopped thinking about it, I'm going to take a break from thinking about it after graduation.
I hope to face myself again, experience various things, and enrich my life.
I hope that my life will become richer and more fulfilling.
I hope I can improve my skills
I hope to be able to come back again when I have improved my skills.
I will graduate on November 29th.
I would like to express my gratitude to all of you, and I love the call and response with my fans.
I love the call and response with my fans, so I hope to get a lot of cheers from them on the day.
Yes, and then, yes, everyone will be there.
Yes, and yes, everyone!
Yes, and then, yes, everyone!
Yes, and yes, and yes, and yes, and yes, and yes, and yes, and yes, and yes, and yes.
I hope we can create a fun space for everyone.
The last leg of this fall tour that started in September
It's not something special, but rather something that we have experienced so far.It's not something special, it's more about what we've experienced and what we've done so far.
I hope we can show what we have experienced and what we have done so far at Yokohama Arena.
So whether you are coming to Yokohama Arena or watching the live viewing or the live broadcast, please give us your support.
I hope you will all give me your support.
Thank you very much for your support.
Thank you very much.
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement by Miku Hatsune
Late Singing Time
We have different hobbies, different hair, different eyes, different tastes
Maybe I'll say it now with a pounding heart
The amount of information is different
You look like a recluse
But you're doing fine.
You're in love.
I've never lost anything, but it's not zero.
It's just not in the day.
You know Sigh
You know, a girl's sigh
You know you're not gonna make it
The philosophy of never doing it
You know
The journey of love
It's my philosophy
Yeah!
Oh!
Come on! Come on!
Yeah!
Whoo!
You've been worrying so much about rumors, it's exhausting.
Sometimes the truth beats out the rumors.
You didn't ask me to review you.
So you don't do it for them
That's never gonna create love, is it?
I don't know why I'm sharing information with you today.
So someone will give me a compliment?
I'm just waiting.
You know Regret
You know
Oh no, it'll be a lie
Send it right to your mind
After all
You know the country
You know why?
Because we don't have any trust.
I don't accept
Let's walk into dark
Thank you for watching.
You know I regret every time I say it
You know it's a lie In my life
Philosophy
Do you know?
And the next one...
I thinkI think
Safe. Expand.
I don't approve
I know I'm safe
Philosophy
Thank you for watching!
I want to go to a hot spring on my next vacation.
What do you want to do?
Mizuki Fukumura and Erina Ikuta of Morning Musume。 Mizuki Fukumura and Erina Ikuta from Morning Musume。 Stay!
It's time to say goodbye, so here's an announcement.
We'd like to announce the 73rd single of Morning Musume。 23's 73rd single "Supsuko Fever, Bake Up Call Awake Toki Lever Ending Shine" is now on sale!
This is the first single for the 17th term members and the last single for me, Mizuki Fukumura!
It's No. 2 on the Oricon Surprising Chart! Thank you so much for your support!
I hope many people will continue to listen to it. Please check out the music video!
And please check out the music video! 23 Concert Tour Autumn Lever Ending Shine Show is now underway!
The only shows left are the Sapporo concert on November 25th and the Yokohama Arena concert on November 28th and 29th.
This is where I, Mizuki Fukumura, will graduate.
I will do my best! Thank you for your support!
There will be live viewing on November 28th and 9th, and a live broadcast on November 29th on Teleasa Channel 1.
If you can't make it to the venue, please come to your nearest movie theater and watch the live broadcast!
And on October 30th, my birthday, Morning Musume。 23 Mizuki Fukumura's last photo show
We held an event to celebrate the release.
I was so happy that so many people got it, and it is still on sale, so please get it!
On December 29th, I will be performing with Angstrom at Countdown Japan!
I'm going to appear on Countdown Japan again, as I did last year.
I'm going to appear on Countdown Japan with Angelem again, as I did last year, and I hope we can make Hello Project more exciting.
Hello Project 2024 Winter 3 of us will start on January 2, 2024.
I know it's a bit personal, but it's going to be our 13th anniversary and 14th year.
I'll be celebrating it alone.
I'm going to do my best as Morning Musume。 24 and A team. Morning Musume。 24 and I will do our best as A team.
Tsubaki Factory and BEYOND will be participating together as A team.
We are 3 of us, so I hope we can give the best performance as one team.
We will do our best.
Hello! Project members will appear on the show more and more!
Project members every Wednesday, so please subscribe to our channel!
This time we're joined by Mizuki Fukumura and Rina Ikuta from Morning Musume・23!
Good bye!
Thank you for watching!